&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：如果在本例中使用数字和之间的双等号
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If you use a double equals between, in this case, a number and
保存数字的数组。
an array that holds the number.
这真是个糟糕的主意。
This is a really terrible idea.
您永远不应该编写像这样将基元与数组进行比较的代码。
You should never write code that compares a primitive to an array like that.
但是如果你这样做了，如果由于某种原因你写了一个不能
But if you did, if for some reason you wrote a function that couldn't
控制某人是否传递了一个数字或
control whether somebody passed a number or
一个包含数字的数组，它会强制工作吗？
an array with a number in it, would it work coercively?
在这个特殊的情况下，是的，但它应该吗？
In this particular case, yes, but should it?
哦，为什么比起作用更重要呢？
Ooh, and why is more important, even, than does it work?
为什么这个会管用？
Why would this one work?
为什么一个数字会以某种方式强制等于保存该数字的数组？
Why would a number somehow be coercively equal to an array holding that number?
并且当然仅在该阵列仅具有单个数字的情况下，
And certainly only in the case where that array only has the single number,
如果它有多个数字就不会了，对吧？
not if it had multiple numbers, right?
所以我们再来一次
So let's again,
让我们调用该算法来查看幕后实际发生了什么。
let's invoke that algorithm to see what is actually happening under the covers.
来了解Double Equals在做什么。
To get a sense of what double equals is doing.
首先，它试图比较workshop1Count和workshop2Count。
First, it tries to compare workshop1Count and workshop2Count.
这就是=。
That's the ==.
它将workshop1Count转换为其原始形式，即其编号。
It turns workshop1Count into its primitive form, which is its number.
但是workshop2Count是一个数组，所以它首先要做的是说to Primitive。
But workshop2Count is an array, so what it first does is say toPrimitive.
数组的toPrimitive发生了什么？
What happens to the toPrimitive of an array?
它自己串起来，所以我们最后得到第5行，
It stringifies itself, so then we end up with line 5,
42=“42”，对吗？
42 == "42", right?
但那只是因为那个奇怪的数组字符串化
But that’s only because of that weird array stringification
这不包括括号。
that doesn’t include the brackets.
所以它几乎是意外地在这里工作。
So it’s almost accidentally working here.
并且只是意外地工作，因为数组中只有一个值。
And only accidentally working because there is only one value in the array.
你和我一起吗？
You with me?
现在我们有两种不同的类型，我们有一个数字和一个字符串。
Now we have two different types, we have a number and a string.
这里有两个选择。
There's two options here.
我们可以把数字变成一个字符串
We could either make the number into a string and
比较字符串，或将字符串转换为数字并比较数字。
compare the strings, or make the string into a number and compare the numbers.
算法中发生哪种情况？
Which one happens in the algorithm?
它更喜欢-&gt；&gt；扬声器2：数学化。
It prefers- &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Numerification.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：数字比较，因此字符串成为数字，并且
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Numeric comparison, so the string becomes the number, and
注意这里，第6行，它做了一个三重等于，因为现在类型是相同的。
notice here, line 6, it does a triple equals because the types are now the same.
&GT；&GT；凯尔·辛普森：你遵循这条推理路线吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: You follow that line of reasoning?
这显然是一个人为的例子，但是
Now this is obviously a contrived example, but
这里的重点是，即使它起作用，也不意味着你应该使用它。
the point here is that even if it works, that doesn't mean you should use it.
我认为这是一个明显的例子
This is one of those clear examples I think
强迫对我们来说是一件非常不好的事情。
where coercion is a very bad thing for us.
你应该减少表面积，而不是比较数字和
You should reduce the surface area and not make comparisons between numbers and
数字数组。
arrays of numbers.
这在编程中甚至没有任何意义。
That doesn't even make any sense in programming.
然而，这就是我们大多数被咬的角落里的箱子所在的地方，
And yet that's where most of our corner cases that we get bitten by are,
因为我们做的都是多态打字。
because we do all of that polymorphic typing stuff.
我们永远不应该那样做。
We should never do that.
并且您不应该通过使用三重等于来修复这个问题。
And you shouldn't fix this problem by using triple equals.
好的，这里最重要的外带，这里的修复是不使用三重等于。
Okay, most important take-away here, the fix here is not to use triple equals.
三倍等于会让你看不到真正的问题，
Triple equals prevents you from seeing the real problem,
那就是你一开始就做了一个糟糕的比较。
which is that you're making a terrible comparison in the first place.
你应该做的就是修复它，这样你所做的比较才有意义。
What you should do is fix it so that the comparisons that you're making make sense.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yes.
&gt；&gt；演讲者3：我的意思是，我知道你这样做是为了证明一个观点，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: I mean, I understand you did this to demonstrate a point,
但如果我像这样看代码，
but if I would look at code like this,
你不会说那个人有更大的问题吗？
wouldn't you say that that person has bigger problems than that?
&GT；&GT；Kyle Simpson：这正是我的观点。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That's exactly my point.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：是的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Yeah.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这里有更大的问题。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: There are bigger problems here.
这不是一个，你应该这样去使用双等于。
This is not a, you should go use double equals this way.
这是，这就是人们抱怨的双等号，
This is, this is what people complain about with double equals,
他们说双倍等于是问题所在。
and they're saying that double equals is the problem.
真正的问题是你在做一个毫无意义的比较。
And the real problem is that you're making a nonsensical comparison.
双等于不是错的那个。
Double equals isn't the one that's at fault.
而三倍等于只会掩盖它，它并不能解决真正的问题。
And triple equals only covers it up, it doesn't fix the real problem.
如果你做了明智的比较，
If you make sensible comparisons,
就像数字到实际数字的字符串表示一样，
like a string representation of a number to the actual number,
这是一个明智的比较，强迫在那里是完全有意义的。
that's a sensible comparison and coercion makes complete sense there.
但是如果你把一些东西和一些完全不同的东西进行比较
But if you compare something to something entirely different and
它偶然起作用了，这是不明智的。
it accidentally works, that's not sensible.
这不合理。
That's not reasonable.
我同意你的观点，我们看到的结果是，你为什么要这么做？
I agree with you that the outcome that we see is, why would you do that?
但我不倾向于说JavaScript在这里设计得很差。
But what I don't tend to do is say JavaScript was poorly designed here.
有历史原因
There are historical reasons for
为什么它甚至允许两个原语进行比较。
why it allowed even the two primitives in a comparison.
如果我是设计强制的，我会做所有其他的强制，但是
If I were designing the coercion, I would of done all the other coercions but
不包括这两个原语，因为在我看来唯一的一种
not included the two primitives, because in my opinion the only kind of
应该可能的非原始比较是身份比较。
non-primitive comparison that should ever be possible is the identity comparison.
对原始人的强迫是疯狂的。
Coercion with primitives is crazy.
但是，对原语进行强制的历史原因之一是
But one of the historical reasons for the coercion with primitives is that in
以前你做了newString，现在你有了一个对象。
the olden days you did newString, and now you have an object.
但你不认为它是一个物体，
But you don't think of it as being an object,
你认为它是原始的。
you think of it as being the primitive.
所以他们允许非原始的强制下来
So they allowed that non-primitive to coercively down coerce
其原始等价物。
itself to its primitive equivalent.
这就是为什么算法有类似的东西。
That's why the algorithm has something like that.
我不会写那个代码，但这就是它存在的原因。
I wouldn't write that code, but that's why it's there.
因此，在我看来，很难说这是一个糟糕的设计。
So it's hard to say that's a poor design, in my opinion.